resultsmail.com 2019-05-21

# ResultsMail - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

Last Updated 5/24/2018

At ResultsMail™, we respect the privacy needs of our valued customers and members. This Privacy Policy outlines what specific information is gathered on the ResultsMail site and how that information is used.

Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our customers. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free to Contact Us.

**Information Collection and Use**

ResultsMail explicitly asks when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Your personal information is used to create your personal access to products on the site, and to contact you in the course of using the products. Financial information that is collected is used to verify identity, and to bill either you or your company for products and services, as applicable. 

Once an individual signs up for an account to use the ResultsMail application we collect usage statistics associated with each account. This data is used to help us support each individual customer as necessary as they use the application, to help us troubleshoot issues with the application, as well as determine other usage trends. Demographic and profile data collected by ResultsMail may be used to tailor the Website or any requested email communications, and to display information that is more relevant to you. 

Under no circumstances will ResultsMail make any personal information about an individual user available to anyone.

Your email address is used to only send you information that you have requested. As part of your use of any ResultsMail product, ResultsMail allows you to elect to receive, or not receive, certain information from ResultsMail or its partners. ResultsMail adheres strictly to permission-based email policy. Except as mentioned above, ResultsMail will not send you unsolicited email information, commercial offers or advertisements ResultsMail will not sell, rent, or loan our contact lists or our customer's contact lists (including customer data) to any outside firms nor will ResultsMail use customer contact lists for our own marketing purposes. All emails that you have requested will have an option to unsubscribe. Unsubscribe requests are fulfilled within minutes and no further communications will be sent to users who have stated that they do not wish to receive the specified information. All ResultsMail partners who offer you information via email from our Website must adhere to this unsubscribe policy.

While IP addresses (address of a computer) are logged to track a user's session, the user's identity is anonymous. Tracking IP addresses gives ResultsMail information about which parts of our site are used most often and what information is viewed. IP addresses are not linked to anything that can personally identify a visitor. Thus, session details are tracked, but the user is anonymous.

**Contact Lists, Campaign Content and Campaign Reports**

ResultsMail ensures that all contact lists, email content and reports remain private and confidential. ResultsMail may scan the content of your campaigns to ensure it complies with our Terms of Use — to protect against defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, obscene, profane, or threatening material that is racially or ethnically offensive. ResultsMail will not sell, rent, loan or invite external access to a customer's contact lists. Nor will ResultsMail themselves use customer's contact lists for any purpose.

**Communications from the Site**

Special Offers and Updates

We send all new users a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user's wishes.

**Sharing**

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Business Transitions

In the event ResultsMail goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the link to unsubscribe from the mailing on the email or selecting to not receive this communication in their online account settings.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, ResultsMail, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Surveys [ & Contests]**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Tell-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. ResultsMail will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. ResultsMail stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact ResultsMail at privacy@resultsmail.com to request the removal of this information from our database.

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, such as credit card number and/or social security number, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - Transport Layer Security (TLS). While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon appearing in the Web browsers becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'. To learn more about TLS, follow this link <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security>.

**Credit Card Information**

ResultsMail allows you to purchase email marketing services. When credit card billing is chosen, information is transferred to ResultsMail's Credit Card Authorization Partner, Authorize.net, using industry-leading, secure transmission technology including TLS and HTTPS (the transmission standard used for transactions by major financial institutions). The information is then encrypted and stored securely so that it is ready to handle your transactions. Financial transactions are verified through GeoTrust®, a leading provider of Internet security solutions. GeoTrust is accredited by all major Security, Privacy and Certification Authorities (CAs).

While we use TLS encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage, in a locked and guarded facility.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can Contact Us.

**Supplementation of Information**

In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

**Address Verification**

We use Authorize.net to verify a user's address against their credit card during the authorization process of the credit card.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

Your personal information has been provided to us by you when you signed up for an account to use the ResultsMail service. You can access it and make corrections to it from within your account.

You can review and update your account information, including your organizational information and email address, by logging in and then clicking on the "My Account" tab. Account information, such as your username and password, can be changed by logging in and then clicking on the "Username and Password" tab within the My Account section. If you wish to suspend or cancel your account, you can contact us via our Help feature online or call 888-737-6245.

We will retain and use your information as long as your account is active as well as is necessary to comply with our obligations under this privacy statement and US law.

Concerning your personal data received or transferred, we are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

**International Use**

We are located in the United States of America. You acknowledge and consent to the fact that personal information stored or processed in the United States will be subject to the laws of the United States, including the ability of governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies of the United States to obtain disclosure of your personal information.

With regards to the EU General Data Protection Regulation, concerning your data, we are a data controller, and concerning your contacts' information, we are a data processor.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

## Start Getting Results From Your Email - Sign Up Free Today!
